WONG HAU CHENG

ELECTRONIC & COMPUTER ENGINEERING STUDENT

PORTFOLIO:

https://wonghaucheng.netlify.app

CONTACT

Mobile: +65 9398 3576

E-mail: S10194108@connect.np.edu.sg Address: Jurong West Street 61, BLK

651B #14-362 S(642651)

EDUCATION

DIPLOMA IN ELECTRONIC
 & COMPUTER
 ENGINEERING | NGEE
 ANN POLYTECHNIC

2019 - 2023

• GCE 'N' LEVEL | JURONG WEST SECONDARY SCHOOL

2014 - 2018

PROFILE

A diligent and outgoing 22-year old Engineering student from Ngee Ann Polytechnic. Aspiring to have a career as a Software Engineer, I am not afraid to expand my knowledge in Software Engineering by being open-minded and exposing myself to different areas as well. My personal goal is to have a career I can be proud of when I look back upon my achievements and to be able to provide for my family.

WORK EXPERIENCE

INTERNSHIP AT CREATIVE TECHNLOGY

Tester | Mar 2022 - August 2022

- Identify, document, and track software defects using defect tracking tools.
- Generating test reports and providing insights of the quality of Software
- Support supervisors with firmware/hardware updates
- Work closely with the development team to resolve issues and verify fixes.
- Collaborating with developers and managers to reach quality goals and requirements.

SGUNITED PROMOTER

Awareness Ambassador | Aug 2020 - Sept 2020

- Raising awareness about a new government job website
- Answering queries

SKILLS

SOFT SKILLS

Interpersonal skills Open-minded Ownership Fast Learner Self-developmental

HARD SKILLS

C and C# Language
Programming
Cloud Computing (AWS)
Microsoft Office Suite
Tinkercad
EagleCad
Arduino
Linux Virtual Box (VM)
Soldering
MiniTab
Python
HTML/CSS/Javascript
Git

CO-CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

BASKETBALL CLUB

Jurong West Secondary School | 2017 - 2019

- Represented team to compete in B-Division Basketball
- Participated actively in basketball camps
- Trained vigorously every week

RED CROSS YOUTH

Cadet | 2015 - 2017

- Awarded Best Cadet of the Month 2016
- Represented batch to march for the prestigious Speech Day
- Attended and participated all camps

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

RED CROSS YOUTH

Fundraiser | 2016 - 2017

• Fund-raised for beneficiaries